freefilefillableforms.com 2012-06-21

# IRS Privacy Policy

Para ver esta página en español haga clic aquí.

**IRS Privacy Policy  
****Your Privacy Right** **s  
IRS Office of Privacy  
Access to Privacy Impact Assessments  
Statistical Information  
Security  
If You Send Us Information Online  
Customer Surveys  
****Cookies  
Links to Other Sites**

* * *

### IRS Privacy Policy

You have entered the Internal Revenue Service's website, an official United States Government System. The IRS uses this website to provide information about IRS services and programs. This website includes specific applications which provide more services or enable us to respond to specific questions from Web site visitors.

We will not collect personal information about you just because you visit this Internet site. There are applications on this website that provide you with the opportunity to order forms, ask questions requiring a response, sign up for electronic newsletters, participate in focus groups and customer surveys, or learn the status of filed returns or anticipated payments. Using these services is voluntary and may require that you provide additional personal information to us. Providing the requested information implies your consent for us to use this data in order to respond to your specific request.

* * *

### Your Privacy Rights

The IRS is committed to protecting the privacy rights of America's taxpayers. These rights are protected by the Internal Revenue Code, the Privacy Act of 1974, the Freedom of Information Act, and IRS policies and practices. For more information about these laws, visit the IRS Electronic Freedom of Information Act Reading Room.

* * *

### IRS Office of Privacy

The Internal Revenue Service's Privacy Office ensures that your personal information is protected whenever you visit the IRS website. If you have any questions or comments regarding the IRS's website privacy policy, please contact us at the address below.

Director, Office of Privacy, Governmental Liaison and Disclosure  
Internal Revenue Service  
Room 7050 OS:P  
1111 Constitution Ave. NW  
Washington, DC 20224

BEFORE YOU WRITE, note that we cannot assist you with any type of tax matter. Our office may only address questions about IRS privacy policies or concerns you may have regarding how IRS uses and collects personal information.

* * *

_**PLEASE NOTE:**_ Do not respond to unsolicited e-mails that claim to come from the IRS, or any e-mail from an unknown party asking you to submit personal, tax, or financial data. The IRS does not use email to request this type of information. Forward suspicious e-mails to: [phishing@irs.gov](mailto:phishing@irs.gov) .

For more information contact the Treasury Inspector General for Tax Administration (TIGTA) at 800-366-4484 or visit the [TIGTA website](http://www.treas.gov/tigta).
